hi everybody welcome to the server photo
大家好，欢迎来到服务器图片
Oh a new trees and all favor
哦，一棵新树，众人宠爱
it is the standard sly I'm not going to
这是我不会的标准狡猾
talk about this I'm Ching hai Chang I'm
说说这个，我是青海昌
a so that 3.1 and photo Oh coach badly I
这样3.1和照片哦，教练我很糟糕
also working on South select three
还在南方选择三个
thorough implementation and the security
彻底的实施和安全
jsr JCCC and jasp I so I will let at
jsr JCCC和jasp我会在
introduce himself
介绍自己
alright I know in my name's ed burns and
好吧，我知道我以爱德·伯恩斯的名字
I'm very happy to be here
我很高兴来到这里
given the servlet for talk this has been
鉴于servlet可以进行交谈
many years of Java one trying to get the
多年的Java试图获得
servlet for respect done and the Java EE
尊重您的servlet和Java EE
eight SPECT on it's been quite a long
八个SPECT已经很长了
journey for both technical business and
技术业务和
organizational reasons but we're happy
组织原因，但我们很高兴
to have it finally done we think there's
最终完成它，我们认为
a lot of great stuff in in the spec not
规范中有很多很棒的东西
just in survival but in all of a II and
只是生存而已
I hope to convince you of that today
我希望今天能说服你
Shing why and I hope to convince you of
炫耀为什么，我希望说服您
that today I think this is set up to
今天我认为这是为了
auto-advance that's what's doing me in
自动前进就是我正在做的事情
here
这里
mm-hmm oh well have to get that fixed
嗯，嗯，必须把它修好
yeah I have to set that up hold on
是的，我必须坚持
that's terrible slideshows setup show
那是可怕的幻灯片设置显示
that's why is it doing that
这就是为什么这样做
manually all right play from current
从当前手动播放
slide sorry about that
对此感到抱歉
so I've been doing specs for a while JSF
所以我一直在做规范JSF
and servlet expect leads and also been
和servlet期待潜在客户，并且
an expert group member for a lot of
许多专家小组成员
different specs written a few books
不同的规格写了几本书
about Java and a lot of conference
Java和很多会议
speaking on this topic and with the
谈论这个话题，并与
coming of the Eclipse Foundation and the
Eclipse Foundation和
handing off of the Eclipse Foundation
移交Eclipse Foundation
which you'll have quite a bit of detail
您将有很多细节
on later I hope to still be able to do
希望以后还能做
that but in collaboration with whoever's
但是与任何人合作
working on it and in the community so
在社区上努力工作
we've got you've got a lot of talks to
我们有很多的要谈的话题
choose from I'm very honored that you
选择，我很荣幸您
chose ours and I want to make that
选择了我们的，我想做到这一点
investment worth your time a bit of
值得您花些时间的投资
high-level content on the contemporary
当代的高级内容
and historical role of servlets
servlet的历史地位
particularly taking a micro services
特别是微服务
perspective and a historical micro
观点和历史微观
services perspective on this and the
服务的观点
heart of the talk is mostly shewag
谈话的重点主要是shewag
giving the new features instead of four
提供新功能，而不是四个
and then we'll have some stuff on
然后我们将有一些东西
opening up Java EE and then a summary
打开Java EE，然后进行总结
living that the only we only have 45
活着，只有我们只有45
minutes for our session today I don't
今天我们会议的时间
know if we'll have time for questions
知道我们是否有时间提问
but I will be out in the hacker garden
但是我会在黑客花园里
and I'll be here all week you can catch
我整周都会在这里，你可以赶上
me there and also on the booth floor so
我在那里，也在展位上，所以
let's get into the historical portion
让我们进入历史部分
micro mano
微型马诺
oh no I put up here j2ee servlets a very
哦，不，我在这里将j2ee servlets非常
early Java micro services platform so
早期的Java微服务平台如此
hmm what's the right way to start with
嗯，什么是正确的开始
this all right who was using servlets in
没错，谁在使用servlet
2000 anyone okay who started using
2000开始使用的任何人都可以
service in like 2005 right and who is
像2005年这样的服务是谁
still using sort of what's today
仍然使用今天的东西
all right all right all right so it's
好吧好吧好吧，这是
been around now this micro services term
这个微服务术语已经存在了
is a new thing but you know there's
是新事物，但你知道
nothing new Under the Sun really and I
真的没有什么新鲜的东西
would like to take a few slides worth of
想拿几张幻灯片
time to go through this definition what
是时候通过这个定义了
I've determined to be a consent
我已经确定要同意
this definition of what microservices is
微服务的定义是
and see how well historical
看看历史如何
old-fashioned j2ee servlets stack up
老式的j2ee servlet堆积
with my own opinion and analysis you
用我自己的观点和分析，你
probably might have a different opinion
可能会有不同的意见
this is something of a controversial
这是有争议的
topic too so micro services generally
主题也是如此，因此一般来说微服务
are seem to be all small a system that
似乎都是一个很小的系统
is a collection of services each of
是每个服务的集合
which is small loosely coupled and can
松散耦合很小，可以
be composed isolated from other services
与其他服务隔离
very highly internally cohesive it does
具有很高的内部凝聚力
one thing each service does one thing
每项服务做一件事
can be managed deployed and developed
可以管理部署和开发
independent of the others and is
独立于其他人并且是
responsible for owning its own data
负责拥有自己的数据
let's look at each of these here now on
让我们现在来看这些
the small side there's nothing stopping
另一面没有停止
you from keeping your server what's
您无需保留服务器上的内容
small one of the things that we that I
小事情之一，我们，我
learned in doing JSF with is which is a
在进行JSF方面学到的是
web framework is this challenge of
Web框架是这个挑战
trying to design something where it's
试图在哪里设计东西
easy to do the right thing and and
容易做正确的事，并且
harder but not impossible to do the
很难但并非没有可能
really wrong thing because a lot of
真的是错误的事情，因为很多
times you need to do the wrong thing to
有时候你需要做错事
you know get the job done so servlet
您知道完成工作，因此servlet
with it's very easy to use HTTP session
使用HTTP会话非常容易
and a lot of the properties that it
以及它的许多特性
offers in terms of being ubiquitously
提供无处不在
available and usually reliable and then
可用并且通常可靠，然后
over the years app servers have added
多年来，应用服务器已添加
clustering and failover to the HTTP
群集和故障转移到HTTP
session so we did a lot of stuff to make
会议，所以我们做了很多事情
it easy to really abuse that thing so
真的很容易滥用那件事，所以
servlet in that sense is small you can
从这个意义上讲，servlet很小，您可以
do it but you have to work a little hard
做到了，但你必须努力一点
to make sure it stays small so I'll give
确保它很小，我会给
that a maybe loosely coupled well
也许是松散耦合的
filters can compose pretty well that's
过滤器可以很好地构成
what they're designed to do the filter
他们设计用来过滤的东西
Jain concept is expressly designed to
in那教的概念是专为
support composing and if you have a
支持撰写，如果您有
system that's composed of a number of
系统由许多
different wores you can kind of consider
您可以考虑不同的穿着
them to be composable as well isolated
它们是可组合的，也很孤立
from other services this is generally
从其他服务通常
not how people use serve what's so in
不是人们如何使用服务
the model if one of the reasons why the
该模型是否是
monolith is
整体是
seen as a pattern to get away from is an
被视为逃避的模式是
outage and a servant would prevent the
停电，仆人会阻止
entire rest of the call flow from
整个呼叫流程的其余部分来自
executing that's where the stacktrace
执行那是stacktrace的地方
is we get these big long stack traces in
是我们得到这些大的长堆栈痕迹
Java e my opinion on that now is we
我现在对Java的看法是我们
still have the huge long stack traces
仍然有巨大的长堆栈痕迹
just spread about through all these
只是散布在所有这些
different machines but on the other hand
不同的机器，但另一方面
we have a whole huge raft of logs
我们有一大堆原木
science technologies that are out there
那里的科学技术
to help you make sense of that large
帮助您理解这么大
stack trace so imagine if you could put
堆栈跟踪，所以想象一下是否可以放
your huge stack trace from hell from
来自地狱的巨大堆栈跟踪
j2ee into something like cabana and be
j2ee变成类似cabana的东西
able to analyze it and tear it apart
能够分析并将其分解
like that that might be kind of useful
这样可能有用
but it's just a different approach that
但这只是一种不同的方法
people are using now so in terms of
人们现在正在使用，因此
isolation I would say it's I'll give
孤立我会说我会给
that one a know highly internally
一个人在内部非常了解
cohesive does one thing generally
凝聚力一般做一件事
sleuths are used as controllers or
侦探用作控制器或
filters that act on an HTTP request and
对HTTP请求起作用的过滤器，以及
either pass it on to some other service
要么将其传递给其他服务
or send a response so I would say yes
或发送回复，所以我会说是
they can be said yes to doing one thing
他们可以说是做一件事情
can be managed to poi develop
可以进行poi开发
independent of others this one again
独立于其他人
make it hard to do bad stuff easy to do
很难做坏事
good stuff and j2ee didn't do so well on
好东西，j2ee的表现不佳
this because they came up with this ear
这是因为他们想出了这只耳朵
concept and it let people be very lazy
概念，它使人们非常懒惰
and just say here is this one gigantic
只是说这是一个巨大的
ear it has five wires and whatever else
耳朵有五根电线，还有其他东西
in it and it takes forever to deploy and
在其中，它永远需要部署和
so that one is probably you know I'm
所以一个人可能是你知道我
giving it a yes but it's that's as if
给它一个是，但这就像
you if you restrict yourself to just
你，如果你限制自己只是
wires that you're deploying on different
您要部署在不同位置的电线
containers and servlets responsible
负责的容器和servlet
handing its own data service generally
一般处理自己的数据服务
don't have much in the way of data this
没有太多的数据方式
was always handled by other parts of a
总是由其他部分处理
java ee monolith but whatever data is
java ee monolith但无论数据是什么
sort of what does have it's generally
一般都有什么
not shared with other parts of the
未与其他部分共享
system so I'll give that one yes for an
系统，所以我会给一个
overall rating of kinda sorta you can
您可以总体评价一点
look at servlets as a very early
将servlet视为非常早期的
microservices platform but you know if
微服务平台，但您知道是否
it was the perfect micro-services
这是完美的微服务
platform then we wouldn't be where we
平台，那么我们就不会在哪里
are today
今天
evolve and people change their tastes in
进化，人们改变口味
response to economic trends and popular
应对经济趋势和流行
tools and what is seen as best practices
工具和最佳做法
so talking about trends this is one that
因此谈论趋势是
I really like to talk about we have been
我真的很想谈论我们
doing JCP specs for a really long time
做了很长时间的JCP规范
and I think there's a proven track
我认为这是一个可靠的途径
record of success it's often held up as
成功的记录通常被保留为
slow and ponderous and difficult but you
缓慢而繁琐而艰难，但是你
know you do get results you do get
知道你确实得到了结果，你确实得到了
representation so in the particular
代表性如此
aspect of servlets David we've always
servlet方面David我们一直
adopted and incorporated new features
采用并合并了新功能
from industry trends and best practices
从行业趋势和最佳实践
all along so we've had the packaging
一直以来，我们都有包装
concept of waar for forever
永远的waar的概念
we added asynchronous i/o as that
我们添加了异步I / O
started to be more and more popular when
开始变得越来越流行的时候
you know when it came into the Java
你知道什么时候它进入Java
platform with nio we added that I would
niño平台，我们补充说，我会
also say that we had the ability to do a
还说我们有能力做一个
fully reactive application even before
完全反应性的应用程序
the reactive manifesto was put out there
反应性宣言被放在那里
being able to have back pressure with
能够承受背压
the on data available on write possible
写入时可用的可用数据
methods when dependency injection and
依赖注入和
inversion of control became popular with
控制反转在
the advent of spring and then CDI
春天的到来，然后是CDI
shortly thereafter we added resource
此后不久，我们添加了资源
injection to servlet and and Java EE in
注入到servlet和Java EE中
general and the latest trend of course
当然，最新趋势
incorporating HTTP 2 into the spec so if
将HTTP 2纳入规范，因此如果
you had a Greenfield project from
你有一个Greenfield项目来自
scratch would you choose to use servlets
您会选择使用servlet吗
on that project given the choice of any
考虑到该项目的选择
tools you you had mmm it would be a
您拥有的工具，它将是一个
stretch right but there are some reasons
向右伸展，但有一些原因
where you might want to choose to use
您可能想选择使用的地方
serve vote for green food development
为绿色食品发展服务
and a microservices style let's say many
微服务风格可以说很多
enterprises have very strict standards
企业有很严格的标准
as what is approved and what is not
认可什么，不认可什么
approved a couple years ago I had the
几年前批准的
great pleasure to give a talk and with a
很高兴发表演讲并与
couple colleagues from Lufthansa
汉莎航空的几个同事
Airlines and they have this thing called
航空公司，他们把这个东西叫做
the big book of standards it's probably
标准的大书本
not uncommon in many enter
在许多企业中并不少见
and if you want to use a piece of
如果您想使用
technology and your solution it has to
技术及其解决方案
be in there and those solutions are all
在那里，那些解决方案都是
vetted by their corporate architects and
由他们的公司架构师审核
have met the necessary security
已达到必要的安全性
requirements and legal requirements and
要求和法律要求以及
indemnification and support all these
赔偿和支持所有这些
important enterprise concerns so you
重要的企业问题，所以你
might be in such a shop and you have
可能在这样的商店里，你有
basically have to use whatever you're
基本上必须使用您所使用的
given in terms of j2ee or servlets and
根据j2ee或servlet给出
you might want to take advantage of the
您可能想利用
micro services architecture but not be
微服务架构，但不是
able to use all the different kinds of
能够使用所有不同种类的
tools
工具
that's one reason it also could be that
这也是原因之一
the the team itself is maybe risk-averse
团队本身也许是规避风险的
and try new technologies but adventurous
尝试新技术但冒险
and trying new architectures they want
并尝试他们想要的新架构
to take an incremental approach where
采取增量方法
let's do the new architecture using the
让我们使用
old stack and if once we get the
旧堆栈，如果一旦我们得到
architecture right and we understand how
正确的架构，我们了解如何
to do it then we can take the
为此，我们可以采取
architecture and apply it to the new
架构并将其应用于新
stack so there are some reasons why you
堆叠，所以有一些原因使您
would want to choose servlets for micro
想要选择微型的servlet
services but the more common approach I
服务，但更常见的方法是
would say given by judging by the huge
通过巨大的判断来给出
number of talks on breaking up the
分手的谈判次数
monolith I'm sure if you do a web search
整体式，我确定您是否进行过网络搜索
for breaking up the monolith you'll see
打破整体，你会看到
quite a few of them is using servlets as
他们中的很多人都在使用servlet作为
a stepping stone to a more pure
踏上更纯净的垫脚石
microservices system so I mentioned ears
微服务系统，所以我提到了耳朵
that have wires you know separating out
有你知道分开的电线
those into separate wires another
那些分开的电线
approach that people do is to stand up
人们要做的就是站起来
rest services in front of their existing
在现有服务之前休息
wores
穿着
and then eventually decompose those
然后最终分解那些
wires so you just have the rest services
电线，以便您获得其余服务
the pure micro services and so that's
纯微服务，所以
kind of the approach so I'm gonna hand
这种方法，所以我要去
it off to Shing Y here to give us the
交给成Y在这里给我们
heart of the talk the servlet for new
讨论的核心
feature review Thanks
功能评论谢谢
thanks to add the introduction of the
感谢添加的介绍
servlet with no micro service now let's
现在没有微服务的servlet
try to take a look on a new feature in
尝试看看中的新功能
the server photo Oh now before I go into
服务器照片哦，现在进入
the new feature I would like to mention
我想提及的新功能
that all we done in the Java EE
我们在Java EE中所做的一切
is available in hip-hop calm and slash
可在嘻哈平静和斜线中使用
Java EE you're welcome to try dissemble
欢迎您尝试Java EE的反汇编
in there is in the Quixote um Java EE
在Quixote um Java EE中
grassfish - sample in the samples there
草鱼-那里有样品
you will see a lot of example and to
您将看到很多示例，并且
illustrate the new features in the Java
说明Java中的新功能
EE in particulars servlet photo now
EE特别是servlet照片
let's take a look on what the HTTP 2
让我们看一下HTTP 2
years now we all know that exceeded HTTP
多年以来，我们都知道超过了HTTP
2 is important
2很重要
the primary focus is in the performance
主要重点是表现
and it has a lot of features to improve
它有很多功能需要改进
the page loading in the browser how do
在浏览器中加载页面怎么办
they do this let's take a look now first
他们这样做，让我们先来看一下
is primary framing now in HTTP 1.1 the
现在是HTTP 1.1中的主要框架
protocol is in clear tags and primary
协议以清晰标签和主要
know though is more compact and
知道虽然更紧凑，
efficient when this transfer across a
当这种转移跨
wire and the second one is the stream
电线，第二个是流
multiplexing now in HTTP 1.1 what you
现在在HTTP 1.1中多路传输
have is one request one respond one
有一个请求一个回应一个
request and one respond and they also
请求和一个回应，他们也
have a feature called HTTP pipelining in
具有一个称为HTTP流水线的功能
1.1 basically it says that you can send
1.1基本上说可以发送
send multiple requests at the same time
同时发送多个请求
so you can request one request - and
因此您可以请求一个请求-
request free but there is a requirement
免费要求，但有要求
the requirement is that the responded to
要求是响应
become in the same order of the request
按照请求的顺序
so it must be respond 1 respond to and
因此它必须是回应1回应和
respond free now there is a problem what
现在免费回复存在问题
happened when you take a long time to
花了很长时间才发生
compute the respond 1 in this case
在这种情况下计算响应1
respond to and respond 3 need to wait
回应并回应3需要等待
and the respond 1 is finished and that
响应1完成，并且
is call head of lime parkland problem
是石灰公园问题的负责人吗
now in htv-2 you can actually send the
现在在htv-2中，您实际上可以发送
respond in a different order
以不同的顺序回应
that is cost-free multiplexing what it
这是免费的多路复用
means is I can send request one request
意思是我可以发送一个请求
to and then request free and then I can
到然后要求免费，然后我可以
send respond to and then respond one and
发送响应，然后响应一个，然后
then respond free so the order of the
然后自由回应，因此
response is not important anymore even
响应甚至不再重要
better actually we can split the request
更好的是我们可以拆分请求
and the response into pieces
和反应成碎片
for example you have requests one
例如您有一个请求
request - and then you were sent back
请求-然后您被送回
part one of the respond one and part one
第一响应的一部分和第一响应
of the respond to and then part two of
的回应，然后是第二部分
the respond one and then part two of the
响应一，然后是第二部分
respond - so this is a very nice feature
回应-这是一个非常好的功能
of the stream of the practicin in HTTP -
HTTP中的practicin的流-
and this allowed us to improve a lot in
这使我们在
the page loading in the browser we can
我们可以在浏览器中加载页面
see more about this later today
今天晚些时候再见
now the third feature that we have an
现在，我们拥有的第三个功能
HTTP to to improve the browsing
HTTP改善浏览
performance is the header compression
性能就是头压缩
now if you try to take a look on the
现在，如果您尝试看看
communication between a given browser
给定浏览器之间的通信
and a server you will notice that most
和一台服务器，您会注意到大多数
of the time a lot of the header they
很多时候他们的头
sent across a wire is actually the same
通过电线发送实际上是相同的
a lot to Heather actually the same for
对希瑟来说很多，实际上对于
example what kind of content type of
示例哪种内容类型的
mind type that a browser will observe
浏览器将观察到的思维类型
they need to send it across a wire every
他们需要每次通过电线发送
time now this is a redundancy now the
现在的时间现在是多余的
way that HTTP - - about two years you
HTTP的方式--大约两年
allow to do the compression in the sense
允许做某种意义上的压缩
that the first time you send a header
第一次发送标头
the second time you send index of the
第二次您发送的索引
header of a particular table which they
他们特定表的标题
re on to the other side so in this case
在另一边，所以在这种情况下
you do need to send the whole header
您确实需要发送整个标头
they only need to send an image integer
他们只需要发送一个图像整数
yes because that table is is a private
是的，因为该表是私人的
between the server and the browser and
在服务器和浏览器之间
the server is not shared
服务器未共享
okay the fourth feature is certain push
好吧，第四个功能是一定要推动
and the server push basically is to say
和服务器推送基本上是说
that okay you allow the server to push
好的，您允许服务器推送
the data to the client I'm going to talk
数据给我要谈论的客户
more about this later
稍后更多
and finally they in this HTTP - we
最后是他们在这个HTTP中-我们
always use keep the conditional life so
总是使用保持有条件的生活
in HTTP 1 yes you can keep the
在HTTP 1中，可以保留
connection alive but you have an option
连接仍然有效，但您可以选择
to turn it off but in HTTP 2 is always
将其关闭，但在HTTP 2中始终
keep alive so you can send the data back
保持活动状态，以便您可以将数据发送回去
and for like this now what happened in
现在因为这样
server photo Oh in Soviet photo if you
服务器照片哦，如果您是苏联照片，
use it then you basically can use
使用它，那么你基本上可以使用
leverage all the feature in HTTP 2 so
利用HTTP 2中的所有功能，以便
you get the primary framing stream
您将获得主要的帧流
multiplexing had a compression and the
多路复用有一个压缩，
connection those thing free
连接那些东西免费
this is transparent to the user so the
这对用户是透明的，因此
only thing that you have to do is to do
您唯一要做的就是做
something special above the server push
服务器推送上方的特殊内容
which I'm going to talk more in HDTV to
我将在高清电视中谈论更多
yours we also have some flow control
您的我们也有一些流量控制
thing that is under the wire you can say
你可以说的东西
I want to turn on or turn off the server
我想打开或关闭服务器
push this part is still working
推动这部分仍然有效
underline the Polacco we're going to
强调我们要去的Polacco
take a closer look on what happen now
仔细看看现在发生了什么
before we go to the server push let's
在我们去服务器推送之前，让我们
try to review what happened in a
尝试回顾一下发生了什么
classical case in servlet now you have a
servlet中的经典案例现在您有了一个
browser the browser will go to get
浏览器浏览器将去获取
indexed or take HTML and then they will
索引或采用HTML，然后他们将
return to the browser go to the server
返回浏览器转到服务器
and then come back to the browser and
然后回到浏览器
the browser will do several things they
浏览器将执行几项操作
will first of all look inside intact out
首先将完整地看进去
HTML to do a passing and then they will
HTML进行传递，然后他们将
found out oh I need a stylesheet and I
发现哦，我需要一个样式表，我
also need
还需要
javascript so after they do this passing
javascript，这样他们经过之后
they will send another two HTTP requests
他们将发送另外两个HTTP请求
called get stylesheet and then return
称为获取样式表，然后返回
and then get JavaScript and then return
然后获取JavaScript然后返回
now this is a very common classical use
现在，这是非常普遍的古典用法
case now let's take a look on how server
案例现在让我们来看看服务器
push can improve the performance in the
推送可以改善
classical case now with this in mind we
现在考虑到这一点，我们
are going to take a closer look
要仔细看看
what is the extra server push now if we
现在，如果我们增加额外的服务器推送量
call the wording from out the RFC the
从RFC中调用措辞
basically say server push allow server
基本上说服务器推送允许服务器
to speculatively send the data to a kind
投机地将数据发送到一种
that the server anticipate the kind of
服务器预期的那种
need trading of some network usage again
需要再次交易一些网络使用情况
the potential latency game now what does
潜在的延迟游戏现在能做什么
this mean okay yeah I love the Senate
这意味着好吧，我爱参议院
data from server to the client and then
数据从服务器到客户端，然后
they are actually with all the kind
他们实际上很友善
asking for it okay now first what is the
现在先问一下好吗
data can they be anything no it must be
数据可以是任何东西，不是必须的
HTTP response right because a browser
HTTP响应正确，因为浏览器
only understand HDTV respond
只了解高清电视的回应
secondly the responded to corresponding
其次是对相应的
to a request right now can it be any
到一个请求现在可以是任何
kind of request it turns out not let's
那种要求原来不让我们
take a look on what the RFC say okay the
看看RFC怎么说
request that they correspond to is
要求它们对应的是
called Palmas that request and you have
打电话给帕尔马斯，你有
three criteria
三个标准
the first one is cashable the second one
第一个是可兑现的，第二个是可兑现的
is cost safe which he sends means
是安全的，他发送的意思是
essentially only the third one yes your
基本上只有第三个是
request cannot have a body now with this
要求现在不能有这个
requirement you can look at the Venn
要求你可以看看维恩
diagram on the right hand side for the
右侧的图表
standard HTTP method
标准的HTTP方法
hashable mean pose get and have and safe
可散列的平均姿势获取和拥有且安全
mean option trades get an had so if you
意味着期权交易得到了，所以如果你
want to be cacheable and safe then it
想要成为可缓存且安全的
can only be get and help in this case of
在这种情况下只能得到帮助
course if you have a custom HDTV method
当然，如果您有自定义的HDTV方法
which is supported in the servlet like
像servlet这样支持
you can define a method called foo and
您可以定义一个称为foo和的方法
in this case as long as they satisfy the
在这种情况下，只要他们满足
criteria of cacheable safe and with our
可缓存的安全标准，并与我们
will cross body then you can still use
会越过身体，您仍然可以使用
the push method now let's take a look on
现在让我们来看看push方法
what we had done in a servlet API now as
现在我们在servlet API中所做的是
I mentioned before the servlet the data
我在Servlet之前提到过数据
that we push across a wire corresponding
我们越过电线对应
to a HTTP request so what we have an API
到HTTP请求，所以我们有一个API
call push builder is basically to
呼叫推送构建器基本上是
construct the corresponding HTTP request
构造相应的HTTP请求
and so you can see the method like add
这样您就可以看到类似add的方法
header method which is get or head or
标头方法是get或head或
your custom cacheable save with our
您的自定义可缓存保存与我们
request body and then you have a curie
请求身体，然后你有一个居里
string and then you can specify a
字符串，然后您可以指定一个
section ID and of course you have to
部分ID，当然您必须
specify the corresponding URL path and
指定相应的URL路径并
then you push now given this push
那么你现在就按这个推
builder you can call us construct the
建造者，你可以打电话给我们建造
corresponding request but still you have
相应的请求，但您仍然有
to give me a way to try to get this push
给我一种方法来尝试推动
Buddha we can get it from the HTTP
佛陀，我们可以从HTTP获取它
request now in the HTTP request the API
现在在HTTP请求中请求API
is called new push builder once you call
称为“新推送构建器”
this you will get push builder and then
这你会得到推生成器，然后
you can manipulate and create the
您可以操纵和创建
request now I would like to mention two
现在请求，我想提及两个
things for this new push builder first
首先为这个新的推送构建器准备的事情
it's called new push builder so every
它被称为新的推送生成器，所以每个
time you call it you may get a new copy
调用它的时间可能会得到一个新副本
of the proofreader object second is what
校对对象第二个是什么
happened when this connection
当这种连接发生
the cry and say I don't want anything
哭着说我什么都不要
from the push server push then again
从推送服务器推送，然后再次
actually turn it off you know in a
实际上关闭它，你知道
political layer in this case the push
政治层在这种情况下推
bill that will return now object so
现在将返回的账单反对
every time you call new push builder
每次您呼叫新的推送构建器
what you have to do is you have to check
您要做的就是检查
whether it is now before you try to use
是否现在才尝试使用
it now to illustrate this let's take a
现在说明一下，让我们来
look on a second diagram and to see what
看第二张图，看看有什么
we can do to improve the performance of
我们可以做来改善
the common use case there are you
常见的用例是你
straight before ok now you still have a
没关系，现在你仍然有一个
browser and the browser will go to get
浏览器，浏览器将进入
the inductor HTML and then the they
感应器HTML，然后
allow it to a servlet and the servlet
允许它到一个servlet和该servlet
internally because the T is the
在内部，因为T是
information you can put in a server yes
您可以放入服务器的信息是
ok T is indexed or HTML and you know
好的T已建立索引或HTML，您知道
you're going to need the stylesheet and
您将需要样式表和
a JavaScript so what you have to do is
JavaScript，所以您要做的是
like this first you get a you get a new
像这样先得到一个新的
push builder and once you get this your
推建设者，一旦你得到你的
return object and you return the object
返回对象，然后您返回对象
you have to check where the T is now or
您必须检查T现在在哪里或
not once you know that thing is not now
曾经没有，你知道那不是现在
then you can start to use it then you
然后您可以开始使用它，然后您
can set the path and then push and then
可以设置路径，然后按然后
once you push in from the container and
一旦从容器中推入
then come back and then once you push to
然后回来，然后一旦你推到
the stylesheet you can do the same thing
样式表，您可以做同样的事情
for the JavaScript and then the server
JavaScript，然后是服务器
will send the push for maths frame to
会将推送数学框架发送到
the to the browser and then eventually
到浏览器，然后最终
they were sent the data and then they
他们被发送了数据，然后他们
will send a body of the inductor HTML
将发送感应器HTML的正文
now I would like to mention several
现在我想提几个
thing about this signal diagram first of
关于这个信号图的第一件事
all we notice that the push builder is
我们注意到，推送构建器是
reused in this case so you have one push
在这种情况下可以重复使用，因此一按即可
builder it was put pushed twice
被推了两​​次的建设者
the first time years you push the
第一次你推
stylesheet and then you also push the
样式表，然后您还可以按
JavaScript now if you share the push
如果您共享推送，现在使用JavaScript
builder they is advantages that you can
建设者，他们是你可以的优势
actually P populate all the information
实际上P填充了所有信息
that is common for this to HTTP method
这是HTTP方法常见的
for example this to I know is scared so
例如我知道这很害怕
I just put dot method get' and then they
我只是把点方法得到'然后他们
may share some common had a live session
可以分享一些共同的现场直播
idea or whatever so you can set up
想法或其他什么可以设置
everything in one push builder and then
一站式构建器中的所有内容，然后
you keep setting the path and push then
您继续设置路径，然后按
you've saved the work you don't need to
您已经保存了不需要的工作
reconstruct the object again and another
再次重建对象
thing that I would like to mention this
我想提的这件事
in here the diagram I say I sent out a
在此图中，我说我发出了一个
thousand and JavaScript here we only
千和JavaScript在这里，我们只
send a push Tomas frame first and then
先发送推Tomas帧，然后再发送
later the server will send the body as a
稍后，服务器会将正文作为
data frame I think it is going to talk
数据框，我想这是要谈的
more about this in a concrete example so
在一个具体的例子中对此有更多的了解
now with this particular set up what we
现在有了这个特殊的设置，我们
have is like this we save the two trip
有就是这样我们保存了两次旅行
we save the trip that is from the
我们保存了从
browser to the server again to ask for
浏览器再次请求服务器
the stylesheet and ask for the
样式表并要求
JavaScript now T is a big advantages
JavaScript T现在是一个很大的优势
because in our previous diagram when you
因为在上图中，当您
travel in data HTML you try to get the
使用数据HTML进行旅行，您尝试获取
stylesheet and the JavaScript but we do
样式表和JavaScript，但我们可以
not immediately together you have to get
不是立即在一起，您必须得到
in depth on HTML first and then you have
首先深入了解HTML，然后
to pass the internet or HTML and then
通过互联网或HTML，然后
you have low inside and then eventually
你内心很低，然后最终
find that you actually need it and then
发现您确实需要它，然后
you put a request so this caused a
您提出了一个要求，因此导致了
latency in this case but in here
延迟在这种情况下，但在这里
everything you know you need it you just
一切，你知道你需要它，你只是
send across a wire and then let the
通过电线发送，然后让
browser pick it up now I'm going to let
浏览器现在将其拾起
air to do a demo on the server push ok
空气在服务器上做一个演示推OK
who is using any kind of Java server
谁在使用任何类型的Java服务器
side web framework of any kind
任何形式的侧面Web框架
right a lot of folks okay keep your
对，很多人都可以，保持你的
hands off those are had them up and if
放手把它们放起来，如果
you're not using JSF put your hands down
您没有使用JSF放下手
okay so we got some JSF users the demo
好的，所以我们让一些JSF用户进行了演示
I'm going to show is based on JSF and
我将展示基于JSF和
it's nice and simple and this is just
很好，很简单，这只是
I'm running GlassFish five and I have
我正在运行GlassFish 5，我有
the primefaces
素面
demo waar deployed and http2 is enabled
部署了演示程序并启用了http2
by default in certain and JSF in and
默认情况下，在某些和JSF中
yeah and JSF 2.3 so you're going to get
是的，还有JSF 2.3，所以您将获得
the features if you're going over H if
如果您要检查H的功能
you're going over HTTP if you're not
如果不这样做，您将通过HTTP
going over HTTPS on GlassFish at least
至少通过GlassFish上的HTTPS
you're not going to get HCB - it has to
您不会获得HCB-它必须
be HTTPS for the server push to work and
是HTTPS，以便服务器推送工作，并且
so you know we're just let's reload this
所以你知道我们只是重新加载这个
page and this is just one of the prime
页面，这只是主要内容之一
faces components and let's take a look
面对组件，让我们看一下
at the chrome net internals localhost
在chrome net内部localhost
and I just look for push promise frames
我只是在寻找推诺框架
these are you can see it's making the
这些是你可以看到它使
request for some of the showcase CSS
要求提供一些展示CSS
files and there's quite a lot of
文件，并且有很多
resources coming in here some jQuery
资源进来这里一些jQuery
JavaScript there's some facelet stuff
JavaScript中有一些方面的东西
that's being templated an inline here so
在这里内联模板化
my point in showing that is primefaces
我要指出的是素颜
six didn't have to rewrite itself to
六个不必重写自己
take advantage of server push the fact
利用服务器推送事实
is web frameworks not just JSF but web
Web框架不仅是JSF，而且是Web
frameworks in general know what those
框架通常知道那些
resources are they know the association
他们知道协会的资源吗
between the pages and the associated
在页面和相关联之间
resources in the case of JSF it's very
在JSF的情况下，
strongly known because we have this
众所周知，因为我们有这个
whole resource loader concept where you
整个资源加载程序的概念在哪里
define your resources to this thing and
为这件事定义你的资源
you say this is my resource loader jar
你说这是我的资源加载器
or you don't have to have it in a jar
或你不必把它放在罐子里
but you put there and then once you put
但是你放在那里然后一旦你放
it there the server knows okay these are
服务器在那里知道这些是
my resources and the page that has a
我的资源和包含
resource dependency on those resources
资源对这些资源的依赖
knows that it's going to be serving them
知道它将为他们服务
so it's
所以是
an ideally suited situation for doing
一个非常适合做的情况
server push so that's the quick demo
服务器推送，因此是快速演示
we're getting short on time so I'll just
我们时间紧迫，所以我只是
hand it back off to Shing line to give
交回盛行给
us some more features
我们还有更多功能
we're friends to add for the demo and
我们是为演示添加的朋友，
now having talked about the server push
现在谈到服务器推送
let's try to talk take a look and
让我们尝试谈一下，看看
another feature called HTTP trailer now
现在称为HTTP预告片的另一个功能
trailer is not something that is for
拖车不是为了
HTTP 2 only we are also happy in HTTP
只有HTTP 2，我们对HTTP也很满意
1.1 so is something earlier
1.1更早
now let's take a look on what it means
现在让我们看看它的含义
now let's let me call wording from the
现在让我从
RFC it says that the sender decided to
RFC表示发件人决定
send metadata in the form of trail of
以尾迹的形式发送元数据
views at the another message the
查看另一条消息
sender's should generate a trailer
发件人应该生成一个预告片
header field before the message of the
邮件前的标头字段
body to indicate which field will be
表示哪个字段的正文
presented in the trailer
出现在预告片中
okay that's uncomplicated now let me try
好吧，现在很简单，让我尝试
to extract the information from this
从中提取信息
statement first of all the trail of view
首先陈述观点
is some metadata can it be anything
有一些元数据可以吗
metadata means header here so it will be
元数据在这里表示标题，因此
a header here okay
标头在这里好
secondly when I call trailer trailer is
其次，当我打电话给预告片时
something that is sent at the end of the
在末尾发送的东西
message so you can see is at the end of
消息，以便您可以看到位于
the message
讯息
and finally for a trailer the sender
最后是拖车的发件人
need to inform the receiver that you I'm
需要通知接收者您我是
going to send you a trailer field in
打算给您发送一个预告片字段
this case they will send you a trailer
在这种情况下，他们会向您发送预告片
header now let's take a look on a
标头现在让我们来看看
concrete example what it means now you
具体的例子现在意味着什么
have a standard HTTP response now in
现在有一个标准的HTTP响应
HTTP 1.1 in order to use the trailer
HTTP 1.1以使用预告片
there is a requirement you need to use
有您需要使用的要求
the strongly transfer encoding here so
这里的强传输编码
in this use a chunk wrong sir
在此使用大块错误的先生
encoding here and then in this case I
在这里编码，然后在这种情况下我
want to let the user know I want to give
想让用户知道我要给
you a trailer the trailer you send at
您的预告片您发送的预告片
the end call foo colon bar food is the
结束通话foo Colon bar食物是
name of the trailer PI's are very
预告片PI的名称非常
and then in order to do this in my
然后为了在我的
request header I have to set a trailer :
请求标头我必须设置一个拖车：
foo to tell them that I'm going to send
foo告诉他们我要发送
you a trailer for you with the name fool
您的名字叫傻瓜的拖车
there is a meaning of the of the RAC
有RAC的意义
statement that I described earlier so
我之前描述过的声明
now now then we have a question here we
现在现在那么我们在这里有一个问题
know that all the trailer trailer field
知道所有的拖车拖车领域
will be a headers like this can it be
将是这样的标题可以吗
any kind of headers okay we can be fubar
任何类型的标题都可以，我们可以
but can it be any kind it turns out
但事实证明它可以是任何一种
against there is a requirement for this
对此有要求
it can be anything but not the pseudo
它可以是任何东西，但不能是伪的
header what is a pseudo header a pseudo
头是什么伪头头是伪
header for request will be the HTTP
请求的标头将是HTTP
method the scheme which is HTTP or HTTPS
方法是HTTP或HTTPS的方案
the authority will be the hose and port
权限将是软管和端口
and also the path so this information
以及路径，这样的信息
you cannot send in the trailer view for
您无法在预告片视图中发送
the respond the status code you cannot
响应您无法发送的状态码
send a trade in a trailer view it must
在预告片视图中发送交易，必须
be saying earlier in the header now this
现在在标题中早点说
is a requirement that you have for the
是您对
HTTP trailer field now then we have a
HTTP尾部字段，然后我们有一个
question yes why the people wanted to do
问题是，人们为什么要这样做
this can you think of any use case why
你能想到任何用例吗
people try to do this yeah good checksum
人们尝试这样做，很好的校验和
is one other thing then the other thing
是另一件事，然后是另一件事
will be the digital signature right and
将是数字签名权，并且
we have more and we have one pretty
我们有更多，我们有一个漂亮
popular use case recently is called G
最近流行的用例称为G
RPC which is our PC protocol developed
RPC是我们开发的PC协议
by gogo and this protocol will require
通过gogo，此协议将需要
two things they require HTTP 2 and they
他们需要HTTP 2的两件事
used the trailer field and in fact this
使用了预告片字段，实际上
feature is requested by the by the user
功能由用户请求
from the from the eg discussion and the
从例如讨论和
bring up they say oh we needed support
带他们说，哦，我们需要支持
to trailer vo so this is a good example
拖车vo，所以这是一个很好的例子
of cooperation between the expert group
专家组之间的合作
and us now given we understand what is a
现在我们知道了什么是
trail of view and how important it is we
观点以及它有多重要
will take a look on what the server
看看服务器是什么
photo done for the API ok the API
为API完成照片好的API
consists of two part one is for the HTTP
由两部分组成，一部分用于HTTP
server requests the other one is for
服务器请求另一个用于
HTTP server respond for the request we
HTTP服务器响应我们的请求
have two ABI one you score is trailer
有两个ABI，你得分是拖车
feel ready the other one you scare
准备好你害怕的另一个
trailer for you the getcha review will
为您预告片的getcha评论将
return a map so we will like fubar that
返回地图，所以我们会喜欢fubar
kind of thing and then for the HTTP
诸如此类的东西，然后是HTTP
server respond you have a set rate of
服务器回应您的设置速率为
view and a get rid of you now I want to
查看并摆脱您，现在我想
emphasize that on the right hand side
强调在右边
the response when you say get and set it
您说得到并设置时的响应
straight up for you you do not set a map
为你挺身而出，你没有设置地图
object here instead you send a supplier
在这里对象，而是您向供应商发送
object here and a supplier
在这里反对和供应商
object is new feature in Jady Jady ka
对象是Jady的新功能Jady ka
and basically you only have one method
基本上你只有一种方法
called get here and which is a
叫来这里，这是一个
functional interface for a functional
功能的函数式接口
interface it means that you can actually
界面意味着您实际上可以
use it in the lambda expression and the
在lambda表达式和
reason why we give us a prior what
我们为什么先给我们什么的原因
rather than a map is by the time that
而不是地图是那个时候
you try to set the supply set the
您尝试设置供应设置
trailer field you may not actually know
您可能实际上不知道的预告片字段
what you try to set for example this is
例如，您尝试设置的是
a checksum you don't do the checksum of
校验和，您不执行以下校验和
your body and you compute everything now
你的身体，你现在计算一切
if you try to set your trailer feel
如果您尝试设置拖车的感觉
earlier then you have to know somehow
早些时候，你必须知道
let them know what is the checksum in
让他们知道什么是校验和
this case I will give you a supplier
这种情况下我会给你一个供应商
function and the supplier function will
功能和供应商功能将
keep track the information and compute
跟踪信息并进行计算
the corresponding to checksum and put in
对应于校验和并放入
the header okay now let's take a look on
标头好了，现在让我们来看看
the HDTV server request now can we just
HDTV服务器请求现在我们可以
call it get rid of you without coloring
称它摆脱你而没有着色
his trophy ready can we do that
他的奖杯准备好了我们能做到吗
it turns out we cannot because the
事实证明，我们不能因为
reason is if you do this
原因是如果您这样做
by that time the true review may not be
到那时，真正的评论可能还没有
ready it's not ready you try to go out
准备好了还没准备好，你尝试出去
call it you will get a exception so the
称它为例外，所以
right way to do it yes you have the
正确的方法是的，您有
Kogi's trail of you ready and then you
Kogi对您的足迹准备就绪，然后您
get a boolean return and then you check
得到布尔值的回报，然后检查
whether the boolean is true if it's true
布尔值是否为真
then you'll get the trail of you and
然后你会得到你的踪迹，
then you return okay now having say
那你现在回去就好了
about the request side we have the
关于请求方，我们有
respond and then respond as I mentioned
回应然后再回应
before you just have a set trail of you
在您确定自己的足迹之前
API and in here you will get a supplier
API，在这里您将获得供应商
and the supplier will be a lambda
供应商将是lambda
expression in this case they will create
在这种情况下，他们将创建
the clear hash map and then they
清除哈希图，然后他们
populate the object here now if you use
如果使用，现在在此处填充对象
the JDK 9 there is a new feature called
JDK 9有一个新功能，称为
map off you can actually simplify the
映射，您实际上可以简化
expression here I'll let you find now in
表达式在这里，我会让你找到
the Java table or you go to a GDK deny
Java表，否则您将拒绝GDK
talk they will tell you ok now notice
谈谈，他们会告诉您，现在通知
that in the AVR no on the response I you
在AVR中，没有关于我的回复
have a get trailer field and you also
有一个预告片字段，你也
have a set you have a saturate of you'll
有一套，你就会饱和
also have a get rid of view why do we
也摆脱了我们为什么
need a get rid of you because you're the
需要摆脱你，因为你是
owner who already said to trailer field
已经对拖车场说过的车主
do you already know what it is why you
你已经知道这是为什么吗
need to get it again it turns out
需要再次得到它，事实证明
there's a reason the reason is this as
这是有原因的
you can see in this example you have a
您可以在此示例中看到
filter in front of servlet and you were
在servlet前面过滤，您就
called to filter inside the filter you
调用以过滤您内部的过滤器
will set the trailer view and then when
将设置预告片视图，然后在
you come to the servlet by that time
那时您来到servlet
someone already said the trailer view
有人已经说过预告片
and the server is also interesting
服务器也很有趣
setting the trailer view but you don't
设置预告片视图，但您没有
want to override everything from the
想覆盖所有内容
filter right you have to know what he
过滤器正确，你必须知道他
the few that does so in this case you
在这种情况下，少数这样做的您
get the trailer filled first and then
先把拖车装满
you recover the supplier one and once
您一次又一次地恢复了供应商
you know the supplier one then you can
你知道供应商，那么你可以
control another supplier based on some
根据一些控制另一个供应商
prior one and then set it back to here
前一个，然后将其设置回此处
so the primary purpose of the gate
所以大门的主要目的
trailer field is to support this
拖车领域就是为了支持这一点
composite trailer for use case okay this
用例的复合拖车好吗
is about all I can say about the trailer
关于预告片我能说的一切
and there's something more about the
还有更多关于
server I will let act continues about
我将让服务器继续运行的服务器
the mapping yep I'll be real quick on
是的，我很快就会知道
this we're getting like five minutes
这大概五分钟
left the mapping discovery feature was
离开了地图发现功能
entirely donated by the community member
完全由社区成员捐赠
argent i'm z' and then we debated it and
银色是z'，然后我们进行了辩论，
discussed it in the expert group he's
在他的专家组中讨论过
now working at a PR on PR server and
现在在PR服务器上的PR上工作，
part of the micro profile effort which
微观配置工作的一部分
is hopefully going to benefit from the
希望将从中受益
EE Foundation thing it allows for
EE Foundation允许的东西
discovering how the current server was
发现当前服务器的状态
reached you not only works for Sur
到达您不仅为苏尔工作
what's not for filters it accounts for
什么不适合过滤器
all the various ways the container can
容器可以使用的所有各种方式
invoke a servlet which many right so the
调用一个很多正确的servlet，这样
claim you think you can invoke a servlet
声称您认为您可以调用servlet
by the container applying the mapping
通过容器应用映射
rules or the application code can invoke
规则或应用程序代码可以调用
any of these methods here and if they
这些方法中的任何一种，如果它们
use that approach then there's an
使用这种方法，那么有一个
Associated set of request attributes
关联的请求属性集
that go along with that that let you
伴随着让你
discover where it was before it came
在它来之前发现它在哪里
through get was crest a 2.4 word or
通过获取被冠2.4字或
include so that's just in keeping with
包括在内，以便与
what the art we already had in the
我们已经拥有的艺术
specification when you ask the request
要求时的规格
give me the serve up mapping it'll
给我发球映射
return this immutable serve up mapping
返回此不变的服务映射
it has an enum property which will tell
它有一个枚举属性，它将告诉
you what kind of mapping it was context
你是什​​么样的背景
route you know exact extension and such
你知道确切的扩展路线等
then it has some other javabeans
然后它还有一些其他的javabeans
properties the match value what was the
属性匹配值是什么
pattern that was actually matched and
实际匹配的模式
the name of the server that was invoked
被调用的服务器的名称
and if you have multiple servlets being
并且如果您有多个servlet正在
called and you happen to call this thing
打电话，你碰巧叫这个东西
it'll give you the name one will be the
它会给你一个名字，将是
current
当前
the one that's currently executing some
目前正在执行一些
miscellaneous stuff we had some encoding
杂项，我们有一些编码
clarifications we did on the request
我们根据要求做了的澄清
side the Earl paths read from the wire
从电线读取伯爵路径的侧面
are specified to be in utf-8 we didn't
被指定为utf-8，我们没有
specify that before although we do allow
尽管我们允许，但在之前指定
vendor specific configuration for
供应商特定的配置
reading the earl path portion some
阅读伯爵路径部分
clarifications on the encoding for xww
关于xww编码的说明
form Earl encoded we added method set
伯爵编码形式，我们添加了方法集
request character encoding to the
请求字符编码
servlet context there is a new XML
servlet上下文中有一个新的XML
element that lets you set that as well
元素，您也可以进行设置
on the response side we have the same
在响应方面，我们有相同的
thing method and an XML element okay and
事物方法和XML元素还可以，
I think you're gonna take us out right
我想你会带我们出去的
yeah we also have some other feature in
是的，我们在
the server photo oh one of them is e we
服务器照片哦，其中之一是e我们
add some API so that we you can
添加一些API，以便我们可以
implement a servlet API eat more easily
实现servlet API更容易吃
what the first one is we have a tin some
第一个是我们有一些锡
default method for the listener and the
侦听器的默认方法和
second one is is in the filter in it and
第二个是在其中的过滤器中
destroy and we also add a helper class
销毁，我们还添加了一个助手类
for the generic filter and an HTTP
用于通用过滤器和HTTP
filter and the only change in the schema
过滤器和架构中的唯一更改
in the web dot XML is we add a new
在Web点XML中，我们添加了一个新的
element called default contact root in
称为默认联系人根目录的元素
the past we can not do it we in this
过去我们做不到
servlet and you have to depend on the
servlet，您必须依靠
party tree way to set a contact root and
设置联系人根的聚会树方法和
we also add a new API to set the session
我们还添加了一个新的API来设置会话
timeout which is in minutes here and
超时时间（以分钟为单位）
then you also have an API to add the JSF
然后您还有一个API可添加JSF
R which is similar to the surface a JSP
R类似于表面的JSP
file sorry okay I will add continues
抱歉，我将添加文件继续
because you're gonna see this in the
因为你会在
keynote but there's one additional side
主题演讲，但还有另一面
that I want to put you'll see this in
我想让你看到
the keynote but I wanted to give my
主题演讲，但我想给我
perspective from the servlet side
servlet方面的观点
and actually if you were in the previous
实际上，如果您曾经在
talk from Linda you got lots of most of
从琳达的谈话中，您可以了解到很多
this too but the challenges I can see
这也是，但我可以看到的挑战
for servlet and EE for J that's gonna be
对于servlet和EE对于J
the name of the thing and eclipse
事物的名称和蚀
servlet has always been revised in
servlet一直在修订
lockstep with the whole EEE platform if
与整个EEE平台保持同步
a stated objective of e4j is to make it
e4j的既定目标是使其
more agile it's gonna be hard to do that
更加敏捷，将很难做到这一点
right
对
also Sarila has extremely high backward
还有Sarila的后退率很高
compatibility expectations and important
兼容性期望和重要
servlet EG members are not full Java EE
Servlet EG成员不是完整的Java EE
vendors so that questions gonna have to
供应商，这样问题就不得不
be addressed we've always kind of had
得到解决，我们一直都有
this little dichotomy where jetty and
这个小二分法，码头和
Tomcat which some of the most popular
Tomcat最流行的一些
containers out there are not full Java
容器没有完整的Java
EE containers you don't get EJB by
您不会通过EJB获得EE容器
default for example or CDI and that was
默认为例如CDI，那是
the difference between the so called big
所谓大的区别
full Java EE vendors WebLogic and
完整的Java EE供应商WebLogic和
WebSphere and GlassFish and pair also
WebSphere和GlassFish并同时配对
and there's also a very large number of
而且还有很多
implementations so the servlet has been
实现，因此servlet已经
a great example of the success of having
拥有成功的一个很好的例子
JCP efforts but it's going to be a
JCP的努力，但这将是一个
challenge to have all those stakeholders
拥有所有这些利益相关者的挑战
that's been my challenge over the years
多年来，这一直是我的挑战
with servlet EG is to keep all these
servlet EG可以保留所有这些
spectacled stakeholders in agreement and
眼镜的利益相关者同意
there's quite a bit of difference of
有很大的不同
opinions we'll see how that goes in the
意见，我们将看看情况如何
foundation yeah that's as I said more
是的，正如我所说的
agile flexible open compatible you'll
敏捷灵活开放兼容，您将
see that in the keynote and that's the
看到在主题演讲，那是
summary of moving Java EE to e4j and
将Java EE迁移到e4j的摘要，以及
let's let string Y close us out with a
让我们用字符串Y将我们封闭
summary of the whole talk ok as a
整个谈话的摘要
summary the server photo Oh bring the
总结服务器照片哦带
HTTP to to the Java EE platform and this
HTTP到Java EE平台的操作
is a significant improvement in the
是对
website and we are also backward
网站，我们也很落后
compatible and you can download the
兼容，您可以下载
grassfish fight all and try out the new
草鱼全力以赴，尝试新的
features in the server folder Oh
服务器文件夹中的功能哦
now one thing that I would like to
现在我想做的一件事
mention is right now phyto only one run
现在提起phyto只运行一次
on
上
gdka it does not run on jdk noggins and
gdka不能在jdk noggins上运行，
we are working on the version fight or 1
我们正在进行版本斗争或1
which will run with the Java SE 9 ok
它将与Java SE 9一起运行
thank you
谢谢
[Applause]
[掌声]